const triviaItems = [
  {
    question: "Which item(s) CAN'T be composted?",
    correct_answer: "dairy products",
    incorrect_answers: ["hair and fur", "coffee grounds", "leaves"],
  },
  {
    question: "How much trash do Americans create each year?",
    correct_answer: "210 million tons",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "100 million tons",
      "480 million tons",
      "60 million tons",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is one requirement for composting?",
    correct_answer: "soil",
    incorrect_answers: ["oil", "rocks", "light"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which item(s) CAN'T be composted?",
    correct_answer: "fats / grease / oil",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "fireplace ashes",
      "fruits / vegetables",
      "cotton / wool rags",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Compost is sometimes referred to by what other name?",
    correct_answer: "humus",
    incorrect_answers: ["soil", "nutrient-material", "waste"],
  },
  {
    question: "Compost helps to reduce _ .",
    correct_answer: "greenhouse gas emissions",
    incorrect_answers: ["bugs", "dirt", "microbial activity"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which item(s) CAN'T be composted?",
    correct_answer: "coal / charcoal",
    incorrect_answers: ["nut shells", "paper towels", "hay / straw"],
  },
  {
    question: "What percent of food scraps and yard waste gets thrown away?",
    correct_answer: "28%",
    incorrect_answers: ["50%", "73%", "14%"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is needed for vermicomposting?",
    correct_answer: "worms",
    incorrect_answers: ["water", "sand", "oxygen"],
  },
  {
    question: "One benefit of composting is _ .",
    correct_answer: "increased soil enrichment",
    incorrect_answers: [
      "increased waste",
      "increased fertilizers",
      "decreased plant matter",
    ],
  },
];
export default triviaItems;
